Jordi Paris Ferrer:
Wrote the framework/skeleton of the pi's (normal) python code. Worked on setting up bluetooth communication on the pi side in software. Spent 3 straight hours fixing raspbian's default bluetooth packages (which were totally broken in our image). Also the encryption on the main python script.

Nate Myren:
Searched for appropriate and compatible hardware. Telling course stuff about it. Telling course stuff about it. Telling ... . Devised wiring scheme for the servo and pi. Designed and printed the servo mount. Ported encryption to the flask backend (more below). Donated personal electronics (RIP 2015-2015 servo)


Colin Li:
Wrote all the servo code (both flask and bluetooth scripts), as well as testing it (such as finding that 0%-100% is not the range of the servo in the library, but something like 2% and 11%). Wrote the entire (minus the encryption addon) flask backend (for iOS).